Guide to the Cindy Domingo Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Cindy Domingo papers, 1973-2009; 5651-003; 16 cubic feet 16 boxes
  - CINDY DOMINGO PAPERS, SERIES I (Box-folder Box 1-Box 16)
    - Press, Triumph over Marcos and Andy Pascua, 1995 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - Philippine Ethnic Art and Culture Exchange letter, APALA Press, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Labor's Voice, 1997 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Grant Letters and Press, 1985-1997 (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Call For Justice, 1989 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Fault Lines: Main Street to Manila, 1993 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - The New Tide, Undated (Box-folder 14/10)
    - Casualties of Law Draft, 1993 (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Fred Galang, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Aquinos and Marcos Press, Part 1 of 2, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Aquinos and Marcos Press, Part 2 of 2, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Miscellaneous Press and Drafts, 1981-2010 (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Caryle Murphy Washington Post Article, 1983 (Box-folder 14/16)
    - St. Louis Post- Dispatch, 1983 (Box-folder 14/17)
    - US Foreign Policy Press, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Hunthausen Statement, 1983 (Box-folder 14/19)
    - Letters of Inquiry- FBI, 1982 (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Malabed Campaign, Part 1 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Malabed Campaign, Part 2 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Sedfrey Ordonez Correspondence, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Miscellaneous Press, Part 1 of 3, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Miscellaneous Press, Part 2 of 3, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 14/25)
    - Miscellaneous Press, Part 3 of 3, 1981-1993 (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 14/27)
    - Maeda Video Project, 1990 (Box-folder 14/28)
    - CJDV Endorser's Lists, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 14/29)
    - Phil Bronstein Press, 1984 (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Appeal for Justice, 1981 (Box-folder 14/31)
    - Psinakis Press, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 14/32)
    - Agenda and Court Documents, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Triumph Over Marcos Uncorrected Proof, Part 1 of 2, 1995 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Triumph Over Marcos Uncorrected Proof, Part 2 of 2, 1995 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Triumph Over Marcos Manuscript and Notes, 1994 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Triumph Over Marcos Preface Draft, 1995 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Triumph Over Marcos, 1995 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Triumph Over Marcos Copy Edit and Critique, 1995 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - Triumph Over Marcos Edit, 1995 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - The Estates of Silme Domingo and Gene Viernes v. Ferdinand Marcos, et al Press, 1 of 2, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - The Estates of Silme Domingo and Gene Viernes v. Ferdinand Marcos, et al Press, 2 of 2, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - CIA Activity Records, Part 1 of 2, 1968-1981 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - CIA Activity Records, Part 2 of 2, 1968-1981 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Press Releases, Part 1 0f 2, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Press Releases, Part 2 0f 2, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 15/14)
    - FWC Slideshow, 1981 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Tom Gerard Press and San Francisco ACLU Case, 1993 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - CJDV Slide Show, 1983 (Box-folder 15/17)
    - Fault Lines Draft, 1993 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Estate of Silme Domingo v. Ferdinand Marcos Papers, Part 1 of 4, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Estate of Silme Domingo v. Ferdinand Marcos Papers, Part 2 of 4, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Estate of Silme Domingo v. Ferdinand Marcos Papers, Part 3 of 4, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - Estate of Silme Domingo v. Ferdinand Marcos Papers, Part 4 of 4, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - Legal Documents, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Legal Documents, Part 1 of 3, 1988 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Legal Documents, Part 2 of 3, 1988 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Legal Documents, Part 3 of 3, 1988 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Legal Documents, Part 1 of 3, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Legal Documents, Part 2 of 3, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Legal Documents, Part 3 of 3, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 16/11)